[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logosbynic.com and in
我是logosbynic.com的尼克
this tutorial i'll be demonstrating how
在本教程中，我将演示
you can create these flat style vector
您可以创建这些平面样式向量
avatars
化身
using inkscape and if you'd like to
使用Inkscape，如果您愿意
learn more about how inkscape works be
了解有关Inkscape如何工作的更多信息
sure to check out my inkscape master
一定要看看我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos
视频
where i go over every tool and feature
在那里我检查了每一个工具和功能
in inkscape and i explain what it is and
在Inkscape中，我解释了它是什么
demonstrate how it works
演示其工作原理
i'll put a link in the description of
我会在描述中添加一个链接
the video if you want to check that out
这个视频如果你想看看的话
so we'll get started here in escape the
所以我们将从这里开始逃脱
first thing we want to do is just set up
我们要做的第一件事就是设置
our documents that we're all working
我们所有人都在处理的文件
with a similar view
有着相似的观点
i just want to come up here to where it
我只想到这里来
says view make sure we have custom
说VIEW确保我们有客户
selected
已选择
we'll come over here to zoom make sure
我们会到这里来放大以确保
you zoom in at one to one
你以1比1的比例放大
and then i'm going to open up the align
然后我要打开Align
and distribute menu with this button
并使用此按钮分发菜单
over here or you could just press
在这里，或者你可以直接按
ctrl shift and a as you can see here
Ctrl Shift键和a键，如您在此处所见
where it says relative to we're going to
它说相对于我们要去的地方
want to have this set to last selected
要将此设置为最后一次选择
and then i'll open up the fill and
然后我会打开填充物
stroke menu which is over here or you
笔划菜单是在这里还是您
can just press ctrl
可以只按Ctrl键
shift and f and we'll have that open as
Shift和f，我们会将其打开为
you can see there
你可以在那里看到
so to get us started basically what
所以，为了让我们基本上开始
we're going to be doing is we're just
我们要做的就是我们只是
going to be using really basic common
我将使用非常基本的通用
shapes in inkscape to put together
Inkscape中要拼凑的形状
avatars or faces and
化身或面孔和
i'll just do one as an example here i'm
我只做一个例子，在这里我是
going to grab the squares and rectangles
去抓取正方形和长方形
tool right here
工具就在这里
and i'm going to click and drag to
我要点击并拖动到
create a rectangle like that a little
做一个像那样的长方形
longer in height a little larger in
个子长一点，长一点
height than it is in width
高度比宽度大
because this is going to represent our
因为这将代表我们的
avatar's head and up here this little
阿凡达的头和上面的这个小东西
note at the top right this little
注意右上角的这一小段
circular note i'm just going to bring
我正要带一张通函
that down like that to give this rounded
像这样降下来，让这个圆润起来
corners
转角
and i'll give this a color just to color
我会给它配上一种颜色
in the face here maybe like a shade of
在这里的脸上，可能有一种阴影
orange or something like that
橙色或类似的东西
over here in the fill tab under the hsl
在这里的HSL下的填充选项卡中
tab i'm just going to adjust the color a
我要把颜色a调整一下
little bit maybe
可能有一点吧
give it a little more vibrance like that
让它像那样更有活力一点
there we go that looks pretty good and
我们开始了，看起来很不错
now that represents that's going to
现在这代表着这将是
represent the head i'm going to put some
代表头部，我要放一些
eyes on here now so let me grab the
现在看着这里，让我拿着
circle tool and i'm going to hold ctrl
圆工具，我要按住Ctrl键
and shift so that it makes a
和移位，这样它就可以
perfectly round circle like that and
像这样完美的圆圈和
just click and drag there we go
只需点击并拖动即可开始
i'll make the eyes black or a dark shade
我会把眼睛染成黑色或深色
of gray like that
像这样的灰色
put this towards the center like that
把这个像那样放到中心
create another eye so i'm going to right
再创造一只眼睛，我要向右转
click this and go to duplicate
单击此选项，然后转到复制
and hold ctrl and move this over here
按住Ctrl键，然后把这个移到这里
like that now i'm going to create
就像这样，现在我要创造
another rectangle right in the center
中间的另一个矩形
here which is going to represent the
这里，它将表示
nose so let me grab the
鼻子，所以让我抓住
the rectangle tool again make the nose
矩形工具再次使鼻子
put that right there
把它放在那里
i want to make this the same shade as
我想把这个颜色改成和
the uh the head here but
呃，这里的头，但是
slightly darker so i'm going to grab the
稍微暗一点，所以我要拿起
dropper tool which is over here
在这里的滴管工具
i just like to press d on the keyboard
我只喜欢按键盘上的d键
to grab that it's a lot more convenient
去抢那个要方便得多
click on that to give it that color and
点击它，给它添加颜色，然后
i'm just going to make this a little
我只想让这件事变得有点
darker like that
像这样的黑暗
looking pretty good now i'm going to
现在看起来很不错，我要去
grab the select tool i want to make sure
抓起我要确保的选择工具
this is all centered up on the page here
这些都在这一页的中心位置
so i'm going to hold shift and click on
所以我要按住Shift键并单击
the head right there and i'm going to
头就在那里，我要
make sure the nose is centered
确保鼻子居中
on the head and i'm going to take these
在头上，我要拿着这些
two circles the eyes hold
眼睛有两个眼圈
shift click them both group them
按住Shift键并单击它们将它们组合在一起
together with this button up here that
再加上上面的这个按钮
says group selected objects
表示对选定对象进行分组
then hold shift and click on the head
然后按住Shift键并单击头部
and then center that up
然后把它放在中心
on the uh horizontal axis like that or
在呃水平轴上，就像这样或者
the vertical axis rather
而是垂直轴
now let me click off of that to deselect
现在，让我单击该选项以取消选择
everything i'm going to click over those
我要点击的所有内容
objects right there
就在那里的物体
so i select them both and just hold ctrl
因此我将它们都选中，然后按住Ctrl键
and scale them up a little bit
并将它们放大一点
you may have to scale them up or down
您可能不得不放大或缩小它们
depending on how big or
取决于多大或多大
small you made them so just go ahead and
你把它们做得很小，所以就这么做吧
manually adjust it as you see fit
按您认为合适的方式手动调整
and what i'll do now is i'll just put
我现在要做的就是把
like a little bit of a little mouth down
就像一个小小的嘴巴朝下
here so i'm
在这里，所以我
going to grab the circles and ellipses
去抓圆圈和椭圆形
tool hold ctrl and shift and click and
工具按住Ctrl和Shift并单击和
drag to create a perfectly round circle
拖动可创建一个完美的圆形
like that
就像这样
and i only want half of that circle so
我只想要那圈的一半，所以
what i'm going to do is i'm going to
我要做的是我要
convert this to a path i'll go to path
将其转换为路径，我将转到路径
object to path i'm going to grab the
对象指向路径，我要抓取
bezier pen which is
贝塞尔钢笔
i'm just going to press b on the
我只需按下b键
keyboard to grab that it's this is it's
键盘抓住它就是这就是它
this icon right here i don't normally
我通常不会看到这个图标
use these tools so
使用这些工具
i just have the keyboard shortcuts
我只有键盘快捷键
memorized and then i want to turn on
记住了，然后我想打开
have snapping enabled and i want to have
启用了捕捉，并且我想要
this one right here enabled that says
这个就在这里启用，它说
snap to cusp nodes including rectangle
捕捉到包括矩形的尖点节点
corners
转角
and this one right here snap to smooth
而这一张就在这里，拍得很光滑
nodes including quadrant points of
节点包括以下项的象限点
ellipses i want to make sure those two
省略号我想确保这两个人
are enabled
已启用
i'm going to snap to the left side of
我要跳到左手边
this circle click
这个圆圈点击
snap to the right side of that circle
捕捉到该圆的右侧
click and then finish the shape up
单击，然后完成形状
around the outside like that
像这样在外面转一圈
grab the select tool hold shift click on
抓住选择工具按住Shift键并单击
the circle so we have them both selected
圆圈，这样我们就把它们都选中了
and go to path
并转到路径
difference and what i want to do now is
不同的是，我现在想做的是
i want to make this
我想做这件事
a shade of red like that this is going
像那样的红色，这就是
to represent the mouth i want to put a
为了表示嘴巴，我想放一个
rectangle up top here to represent teeth
上面的长方形代表牙齿
let me first put this over here i'm
让我先把这个放在这里，我是
going to hold ctrl and scale that down a
按住Ctrl键并将其缩小为
little bit
一点点
let me hold shift and click on both of
让我按住Shift键并同时单击
those objects and make sure i have them
把那些东西拿到我手里
centered up like that
像这样居中
i might want to take these eyes and nose
我可能想把这双眼睛和鼻子
and move them up a little bit
然后把它们往上移一点
i'm going to put another rectangle right
我要把另一个长方形纠正过来
here to represent teeth
在这里代表牙齿
so what i want to do is i want to i want
所以我想做的是我想要我想
to make sure that the rectangle is the
以确保该矩形是
same width
相同的宽度
as this half circle so i'm going to
因为这半个圈，所以我要
click on the half circle up here where
单击此处的半圆形，其中
it says width
上面写着宽度
i'm going to triple click that so we
我要点击三次，这样我们就可以
have it all selected and i'm going to
把它们都选好，我就会
copy whatever that number is i'm going
不管那个号码是什么，我都要去
to hit ctrl c
按Ctrl c键
on the keyboard and now i'm going to
在键盘上，现在我要
create a rectangle so i'm going to come
创建一个矩形，这样我就可以来了
over here
在这里
create a rectangle like that we're going
创建一个这样的矩形，我们要
to want square corners in this rectangle
要在此矩形中使用正方形
so i'm going to click this button up
所以我要点击这个按钮向上
here
这里
to make sure the corner is sharp like
要确保拐角锋利，就像
that
那
and now i'm going to paste the height in
现在我要把高度粘贴到
there so i'll grab the select tool and
所以我将抓起选择工具并
again where it says width
上面写着宽度的地方
triple click that and then just hit ctrl
点击三下，然后按下ctrl键
v to paste the height in there like that
V将高度粘贴在那里，就像这样
that's what i'm looking for i'm going to
这就是我要找的，我要
make that white
把那个涂成白色
to represent teeth maybe make that a
来代表牙齿也许会让这成为一种
little smaller
小一点
i'm going to hold shift click on the
我将按住Shift键并单击
mouth group those two together
嘴巴把那两个人组合在一起
with the group button up here oops
按下这里的组按钮，哦
there we go let me make that a little
我们走吧，让我稍微说一说
smaller again make sure we have it
再小一次，确保我们有它
centered up it looks like it already is
居中看起来它已经是了
and what i'm going to do now is i'm
我现在要做的是
going to add some ears to the sides of
我要在…的边上加几个耳朵
the head here
这里的头
now if you see me scrolling um you see
现在，如果你看到我滚动，嗯，你会看到
me zooming in and out like this you
我像这样放大和缩小你
could just hold ctrl
可以按住Ctrl键
and roll up and down your mouse wheel to
并上下滚动鼠标滚轮以
zoom in and out and to move around the
放大和缩小以及在
page you can just press down the mouse
你只需按下鼠标就可以了
wheel and move around the mouse
滚动并在鼠标周围移动
so let me grab the circles and ellipses
所以让我拿起圆圈和省略号
tool i'm going to hold ctrl and shift to
工具，我要按住Ctrl键并切换到
create another ellipse or a circle
创建另一个椭圆或圆
rather like this
与其说是这样
i want to make this the same color as
我想把这件衣服做成和
the skin tone here so i'm going to grab
这里的肤色，所以我要抓起
the dropper tool
滴管工具
over here and make that the same color
在这里，把它改成同样的颜色
now i want this to be positioned beneath
现在我要把这个放在下面
the head so i'm going to come up here to
头，所以我要到这里来
where it says
上面写着
lower selection to the bottom and click
将选区降低到底部，然后单击
on that and let me just turn off
在那上面，让我关掉
snapping for the time being because that
暂时抢购是因为
may get in the way of where i want to
可能会阻碍我想去的地方
position
职位
the uh the ears here so let me bring
呃，耳朵在这里，所以让我带上
this over like that
这件事就这样结束了
i'm going to hold ctrl and shift and
我要按住Ctrl和Shift键，然后
a little too big position that right
仓位有点太大了，对吧
about there
关于那里
now i'm going to create a a duplicate of
现在我要创建一个副本
this circle by pressing control d
通过按Ctrl d来圈出此圆
and i'm going to make it the same color
我要把它改成同样的颜色
as the nose right here so again we're
就像鼻子一样，所以我们又一次
going to grab the dropper
我要去拿滴管
go like that there we go now i'm going
就这样走吧，我们走吧，我要走了
to lower this down i'm going to lower
为了把这个降下来，我要降下来
this one step
这一步
lower this another step so that it goes
把这个再往下放一步，这样它就能走了
and to do that i'm pushing this button
为了做到这一点，我按下了这个按钮
i'm going to hold ctrl and shift scale
我要按住Ctrl和Shift比例
that down
把那个放下来
and that right there is what i'm looking
这就是我正在寻找的东西
and click on both of these circles so i
点击这两个圆圈，这样我
have them both selected and i'll group
让他们都被选中，我来分组
them together
他们在一起
group selected objects and now i want to
对选定对象进行分组，现在我想
use them for the other ear over here so
把它们当另一只耳朵用，所以
instead of right clicking and going to
而不是右键单击并转到
d on the keyboard to duplicate it and
键盘上的D键复制它，然后
then i'll hold ctrl and just click and
然后我将按住Ctrl键并单击
that
那
and i'm going to lower them to the
我要把它们降到
little closer like that
像这样再近一点
i want to hold shift and click on the
我想按住Shift键并单击
other ear over here i want both sets of
另一只耳朵在这里，我想要两套
ears selected
选定的耳朵
then hold shift and click on the head
然后按住Shift键并单击头部
bit so i can see how this is coming out
所以我可以看看这是怎么出来的
it's looking pretty good one thing i
它看起来很不错，有一件事我
want to do is make the head a little
想要做的就是把头弄得有点
more elongated so let me convert
更拉长，所以让我转换一下
this to a path i'm going to go to path
这是一条我要去的小路
object to path
对象到路径
and now i'm going to go to the edit
现在我要去编辑
paths by nodes tool i'm going to click
按结点路径工具我要单击
and drag over this top portion of nodes
并将鼠标拖到节点的顶部
over here
在这里
and just hold ctrl and move them up like
只需按住Ctrl键并向上移动它们，就像
there because we're going to put some
因为我们要放一些
hair
头发
over the head here and i want to make
在这里的头上，我想要
sure i have more room to work with
当然，我有更多的工作空间
so let me grab this select tool what i'm
所以让我拿起这款精选工具
going to do now is i'm going to create
现在要做的是我要创造
some hair for our avatar here so
为我们的头像准备了一些头发
to do this i'm going to create an offset
为此，我将创建一个偏移量
of the head here so i'm going to go to
头的位置，所以我要
with this
有了这个
head selected i'll go to path linked
选中头部，我将转到链接的路径
offset
偏移量
and that's going to create a copy of it
这将创建它的副本
and the copy is going to be located
副本将被定位到
behind
在后面
the head so let me just come over here
头，所以让我过来一下
and pick a color for the hair i'm going
为我要去的头发选一种颜色
to go with
与之搭配
like this shade of brown over here
就像这里这个棕色的阴影
you're not going to see it change colors
你不会看到它变色的
on your screen because it's positioned
因为它被定位在你的屏幕上
behind the head but once you've done
在脑袋后面，但一旦你做了
that you can take this little node and
你可以把这个小节点
pull that out
把那个拿出来
and you'll notice it's coming out like
你会注意到它就像是
that now let me finalize that by
现在让我通过以下方式来结束它
converting it to a path we'll go to path
将其转换为路径，我们将转到PATH
object to path and i want to grab the
对象复制到路径，我想要获取
select tool
选择工具
and lower this to the bottom so it goes
把这个放到底部，这样它就会
beneath the ears and now i just want to
在耳朵下面，现在我只想
cut off
切断
the portion of the hair that is below
头发下面的那部分
the ears so let me grab the bezier pen
耳朵，让我拿起贝塞尔钢笔
again
再来一次
i'm going to start right about here
我将从这里开始
click to create a point hold ctrl bring
单击以创建按住Ctrl键带来的点
the line straight through like that
这条线就是这样穿过去的
create another point now we can just let
创造另一个点，现在我们只需让
go of control and finish the shape
失去控制，完成形状
around the outside like that
像这样在外面转一圈
grab the select tool hold shift click on
抓住选择工具按住Shift键并单击
the object there and go to
对象在那里，然后转到
path difference and there we go now we
路径差异，我们现在开始了，我们
have
有
the sides of the hair anyway i'm going
不管怎样，头发的两边我都要去
to add some hair to the top up here
给上面的头发加点头发
so to do that i'm going to grab the
所以要做到这一点，我要抓住
rectangle tool again and i'm just going
再来一次矩形工具，我正准备
to create a rectangle over the top here
要在此处的顶部创建矩形
to create some hair to put on top of the
要创建一些头发以放置在
head
头
i'll position this right about here and
我会把它放在这里，然后
i'm going to make this shade a little
我要把这个色调改得稍微深一点
lighter
打火机
just to add a little bit of depth to the
只是为了增加一点深度，
design here and what i want to do now is
这里的设计，我现在想做的是
i want to leave this corner
我想离开这个角落
sharp but i want to make these three
很锋利，但我想做这三个
corners rounded and to do that i'm going
圆角，为了做到这一点，我要
to use a
要使用
live path effect called fillet and
活动路径效果称为圆角和
chamfer
倒角
so let me first convert this to a path
所以让我首先将其转换为路径
i'll go to path
我要去PATH
object to path now i want to open up the
对象指向路径，现在我想打开
path effects menu so i'll go to path
路径效果菜单，所以我将转到路径
grab the path effects menu and right
抓取路径效果菜单，然后向右
here where it says plus
在这里它写着加号
click on plus to add a new path effect
点击加号添加新的路径效果
and the one i'm looking for is corners
我要找的是角落
or the fillet and chamfer path effect
或圆角和倒角路径效果
click on that
点击该按钮
and down here where it says change only
在这下面，上面写着只改变
selected nodes make sure you click on
选定的节点确保您单击
that to have that box text
有那个方框文本
and i'm going to grab the edit pads by
我要去拿一下编辑板
nodes tool
节点工具
and i'm going to click and drag over
我要点击并拖拽过来
this node on the top left then hold
左上角的此节点然后按住
shift click on this click and drag over
按住Shift键单击此按钮并将其拖到上方
that node on the bottom left
左下角的那个节点
and then again hold shift and take this
然后再次按住Shift键并拿着这个
node over here on the bottom right
右下角的节点在这里
so that we only have these three nodes
所以我们只有这三个节点
selected because i want to make these
被选中是因为我想让这些
three corners rounded
三个圆角
now where it says radius i'm just going
现在它说半径的地方，我只是去
to click this little plus icon and
点击这个加号小图标
you're going to notice
你会注意到
it rounds the corners it rounds those
它绕过角落，绕过那些
corners as we do that while leaving this
我们这样做的同时离开了这个
corner sharp
拐角锐利
that right there is what i'm looking for
就在那里，这就是我要找的
so let me let me finalize that by going
所以让我最后说一句
to path
至路径
object to path i can now close out of
对象指向我现在可以关闭的路径
the path effects menu we don't need that
路径效果菜单我们不需要它
anymore
更多
place that right about there this is
把那个放在那里，这就是
starting to come together now
现在开始走到一起
one final thing i want to do is just add
我想做的最后一件事是添加
a little bit of a a little bit of an
有点像有点像
accent piece right here to make it look
重音片段就在这里，让它看起来
like um like light is reflecting off the
就像，嗯，就像光在反射
hair so i'm going to take this
头发，所以我要拿着这个
object i'm going to duplicate it by
对象我将通过以下方式复制它
pressing ctrl d
按Ctrl d键
and then i'm going to hold shift and
然后我要按住班次
click on this one of these lighter
点击这个打火机
shades down here for the for the color
这里的色调是为了这个颜色
we originally used for the hair
我们最初是用来做头发的
to give that an outline otherwise known
给出一个另外已知的提纲
as a stroke now let me remove
作为一种中风，现在让我移除
the fill color from this object i'm
此对象的填充颜色
going to click this little red x over
我要点击这个红色的小x
here to the bottom left
从这里到左下角
and i'm going to hold ctrl and shift and
我要按住Ctrl键和Shift键
scale this down a little bit like that i
像这样缩小一点，我
just want to position this right about
我只想把这个放在正确的位置
here
这里
i just want to take a sample of this
我只想试一试这个
line right here i don't want the
就在这里，我不想要
entirety of this line
整条线路
if you want to come over if you want you
如果你愿意的话，你想过来吗？
can come over here to the stroke style
可以到这里来划水的风格
tab to adjust the thickness of this line
制表符可调整此线条的粗细
yours
你的
the thickness of your line may vary
您的线条粗细可能会有所不同
depending on what you most recently used
取决于您最近使用的内容
so
所以
i'm going to make this a little thicker
我要把它做得更厚一点
and now i just like i said i just want
现在我就像我说的我只想
to grab a sample of this line i don't
要拿到这一系列的样品，我不会
want the entire line so i'm going to
想要整条生产线，所以我要
grab the bezier pen click to create a
抓起Bezier钢笔点击以创建
point hold ctrl bring this straight
按住Ctrl键使其保持直通
through
穿过
like that then bring this straight
像这样，那就直截了当地说吧
through like that
就这样度过了
back to the starting point grab the
回到起点，抓住
select tool
选择工具
hold shift click on the object and go to
按住Shift键单击对象并转到
path
路径
cut path and that's going to slice that
切割路径，这将切开它
into two individual pieces so let me
分成两块，所以让我
click off of that
点击该按钮
and take just this object and just get
只拿这个物体，就可以
rid of that by pressing delete on the
按Delete上的Delete键即可删除
keyboard
键盘
and now we have this i'm going to go
现在我们有了这个，我要走了
come over here to where it says stroke
过来，到上面写着中风的地方
paint and i'm going to adjust the color
涂上油漆，我要调整颜色
of that a little bit
有那么一点
make that little there we go just a
让它变得很小，我们只需要一次
little lighter than the hair over here
比这里的头发稍微浅一点
so if we zoom out you can see we're
所以，如果我们缩小，你可以看到我们
pretty much done we have created our
差不多完成了，我们已经创建了我们的
vector
矢量
avatar i'm going to leave a link in the
头像我要在
description of the video to where you
视频描述您所在的位置
can download
可以下载
12 of these vector avatars for free
其中12个免费的载体化身
and then you can use them however you
然后您可以随时使用它们
want you can mix and match different
希望您可以混搭不同的
parts and elements and
零件和元素以及
pretty much do whatever you want with
几乎做任何你想做的事
them so i'll be releasing them into the
所以我会把它们释放到
public domain so feel free to use them
公共领域，因此可以随意使用它们
however you want whether it be for
无论你想要什么
personal or commercial use and if you
个人或商业用途，如果您
have any questions just leave a comment
有任何问题请发表评论
below and as always
下面一如既往
thanks for watching
感谢收看
you
你